Okay, so I gave that feedback to the
model. I told it to work on the prompts.
I told it to work on the chat user
interface to make it tighter and to stop
the scrolly thing and it did all of
that. It got a bit stuck with the chat
user interface. It made some changes and
the colors were all wrong. And I told it
to fix it and it tried and it made no
difference. And we went backwards and
forwards about four or five times. And
this is the kind of thing that can get
very frustrating and you can start
finding yourself getting more and more
annoyed. But instead, what I did is I
said, "Okay, I tell you what, don't do
it that way. Build a completely
different chat user interface. Just
remove what you did. Try again. It did
it another time and it looks great." So,
that's a good technique to know about.
It's it's a there comes a point when you
get sort of stuck in a rut. You're
asking a model to make a change and it's
making the same mistake or it's just
stuck and there's a point when you can
just say, "Let's approach it
differently." That might be easier than
trying to figure out what's going wrong.
So that's what we did. Anyways, with
that, let's now bring it up. So I'm
going to come here and do mpm rundev to
bring it up. Let me show you what it's
come up with. This is what it looks like
now. Okay. So I'm going to go to
localhost 3000. Here is our website. And
doesn't it look beautiful? Scroll down.
Let's find our way to the digital twin.
Here it is. And I'm going to say hi
there. And you can see first of all that
it's nice. The formatting is good. It
looks polished. It has this thing where
it sort of does a dot for a while and
then it's thinking. It's just running on
my on my local computer which is doing a
lot. So, it's not particularly fast. But
here it comes and it streams back very
nicely like that. Hello, I'm Ed Donna.
Uh, what are you most proud of? And let
it have a think about that. It's going
to have more to say, so it may take a
bit longer, but but I do think I think
that the formatting is really excellent
now, which is which is very nice. It's
got uh uh the same it's it fixed the
problem with the scrolling as I said and
it also has the whole of the prompt in
there uh the the whole of my LinkedIn
profile in its prompt so it's giving
better more rigorous answers. So I think
this is a terrific website. I think that
this chat interface now looks great.
Everything is really good. There's
plenty of room for improvement but for
just just a a few minutes of vibe coding
I think this is a great start. And now
for my master stroke. Everything that
we've done so far has been breaking a
lot of the rules that I said at the
beginning until this point. I am now
going to stop the server with control C.
I'm going to come here to my agent and
this is the prompt I'm writing. Please
now write me a comprehensive tutorial in
markdown that's suitable for a complete
beginner in front-end coding to walk me
through what you've done here. include a
summary of the technology, a highle
walkthrough, a detailed code review with
code samples, and end with five
suggestions for the ways the code could
be improved based on a self review. I've
kicked that off. I am basically having
it appraise itself and give me this
detail. And it's doing that now. It's
building a tutorial. And in a moment,
we'll take a look at what it's made.
Well, that's complete. Let's have a
look. It's here. It's tutorial.md.
I'm going to open a preview by
right-clicking to have a look at the
tutorial that's been written for us.
Professional website and digital twin
chat beginner tutorial. You can see here
there's a summary, there's a
walkthrough, there's a code structure,
there's samples of the code written
here, the styling, the front end and the
back end and how that works, how to run
it locally. It's it's pretty minimal,
but it's a start. And what we can now do
is iterate on it again and say build
this out. give me more. And you can do
that and make sure that it's pitched at
the right level of detail for you. And
that's what you should do now. And do
that with this so that you get to the
point when you really understand. Take
this if you're already familiar with a
front end and you're like, "Okay, I get
it." Uh, but if you're not familiar, use
this as your way to learn about it. It's
both a way to learn about it and it's a
way to challenge and test your your
agent to make sure you're satisfied with
the way that it's done the work. And as
a final point to mention, one of the
cool things about cursor is that because
we can just switch between the different
models, and I guess this is true for the
others as well. We can now have a
different model do a code review of what
just happened. So I can say please do a
comprehensive
code review of this project and write
the results to review.md
including
remediate any any uh remedial actions
needed.
Don't actually change any code. And we
can send this not to codeex but instead
to opus 4.5 the strongest model from
anthropic and press enter. And this
whole context conversation assignment
and work goes to opus now to do a
comprehensive code review. And what
we're seeing here in the thread is not
conversation from codeex anymore. It's
now from opus. And that means we're
getting like a different trained model
with a different perspective to give us
its view on what's happened. And so I
will come back when that code review has
been written. Okay. And that completed.
And we'll find it here in review.md. And
we open that up. And we will find I I
mean I just love Opus. And we'll find
this super comprehensive code review. We
should have had Opus write the tutorial.
It would have been this comprehensive.
Lots of stuff in here. this there's one
that's that's perhaps a bit of a of a
miss about the MMV file, but other than
that, these are things that are that are
lots of good points it makes. I I did I
took a look through it a moment ago and
uh with with sort of action plans around
it. It does a good uh a good dependency
analysis. It does lots of useful things
here and it has some remedial actions,
the critical ones that it's concerned
about the theMV
that's there. it this this is a probably
a real a real problem and uh then that's
a that's not a massively serious one but
probably a good piece of advice. So,
lots of stuff here. That's great. And of
course, what you could now do is go back
to codeex and say, take a read through
this document and implement the remedial
actions or say if you disagree. And
that's a way that you can just call
these different LLMs to have them each
work on a piece of the puzzle together.
And in later weeks when we work with sub
agents with multiple agents, we will of
course be able to do that sort of in
real time collaborating. But this is
this is foreshadowing that functionality
to come. So, this is a really great
exercise using using our models to write
a tutorial and you should keep drilling
down until you've got the detail you
need to understand this and doing a code
review and then remediating the code
review. That is a great way to get good
quality out of vibing on YOLO. And with
that, hopefully you have your own
website and digital twin built and
working. If it's not, remember, be
patient. Simplify simplify. Simplify.
take it back to a simple website, make
sure the website works, and then add
bits in. Particularly if you're working
with with smaller models, that is often
required, but you should get there. You
should have it working. And if you
absolutely love it and you're thinking,
I wish this were my website, well, you
could take my AI engineer MLOps course
to find out about deploying things into
production. Or for this simple one, you
could just ask your model to build you a
tutorial for how to deploy it to
something like Versel yourself. and it
will tell you how to do it. It would
actually deploy it for you, too. But I
recommend just get it to write you the
to-do list and then go and do that
should you wish this to become your
website because hopefully you'll have
something really beautiful. And I do
hope you enjoyed it. Our first real
yolo. We broke all of the rules, but we
didn't break them totally because at the
end we came back and looked in at the
code and checked it. Okay, with that you
are 27% of the way through and that was
a it was a great blue day. The first
blue day. Tomorrow is another blue day
as we build more projects. I'll see you
then.